atlascorps.org 2019-09-26

# » Privacy Policy

**Questions about the Atlas Corps Private Policy**

This website is owned and operated by Atlas Corps. We recognize that visitors to our site may be concerned about the information they provided to us, and how we treat that information. This Privacy Policy addresses those concerns. If you have questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact:

Atlas Corps

ATTN: Communications

99 M Street SE 4th Floor

Washington, DC 20003

[engagement@atlascorps.org](mailto:engagement@atlascorps.org) 202-391-0694

**Website Information Accuracy**

It is the policy of Atlas Corps to present correct and accurate information. If inaccuracies come to our attention, Atlas Corps will attempt to correct them in a timely manner. To report any Website inaccuracies please e-mail [engagement@atlascorps.org.](mailto:info@atlascorps.org)

**Privacy Policy**

Atlas Corps seeks to respect and protect the privacy of our visitors and only gathers personally identifiable data, such as names, addresses, zip/postal codes, e-mail addresses, etc. when voluntarily submitted by a visitor. For example, personally identifiable information may be collected in order to complete a donation transaction or a volunteer application. Atlas Corps does not share lists or other information collected with any other organizations.

It is the policy of Atlas Corps to maintain accurate information on you. If you would like to review information we have about you, please contact us via U.S. mail, e-mail[ engagement@atlascorps.org.](mailto:info@atlascorps.org) Atlas Corps will correct information that is inaccurate.

**Opt-Out**

Visitors may opt-out of having their personal information used by Atlas Corps to send promotional correspondence by contacting Atlas Corps via U.S. mail, e-mail [engagement@atlascorps.org,](mailto:info@atlascorps.org) or checking the appropriate box on the online form.

**Disclosure**

At times, Atlas Corps may be required by law or legal process to disclose information about you to others. Atlas Corps may also disclose information about you if it believes that disclosure is necessary for the public interest and/or safety.

Atlas Corps does not knowingly solicit personal information from children or send them requests for personal information.

**Security**

Our site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. These security steps make it difficult for anyone else to intercept the credit card information you send to us. Companies we work with to process credit card transaction also use high-grade encryption and security protocols. Even though Atlas Corps will take all reasonable steps to protect your personal and financial information, it cannot and does not guarantee its confidentiality or security.

If you prefer, contributions can be made by calling 202-391-0694, or you can mail your donation to:

Atlas Corps

99 M Street SE 4th Floor

Washington, DC 20003

[engagement@atlascorps.org](mailto:engagement@atlascorps.org) 202-391-0694

**Other Web Sites**

Our Site contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website for which Atlas Corps has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on all such sites as their policies may be different than ours.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will note the last update at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. The most recent version of this policy is available for public consumption on our website.
